surfandsunshine.com 2019-02-18

# Disclosure and Privacy Policy – Surf and Sunshine

This policy is valid from 01 January 2012

Surf and Sunshine is a personal blog written and edited by me, Jeana S, and a collection of staff writers or guest bloggers.  If you have any questions or concerns, please contact  Jeana (jeana at surfandsunshine dot com).

I am a full-time blogger.  In order to be able to devote 100% of my time to providing the content for this blog, I do selectively accept various forms of cash advertising, affiliate marketing, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. I believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity.  As the owner of this blog, I am sometimes compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics.

Even though I may sometimes receive compensation for posts or advertisements, I always give my 100% honest opinion, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely my own and will NEVER be influenced by any form of compensation. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog may contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.

The Author shall not be liable for any damages of losses, nor the content of this blog. You agree to hold the author and affiliated parties harmless from any and all third party claims of liability, loss, or expense. The author is not liable if this blog is illegal in the area it is accessed. This author and affiliated parties mean no harm to you or anyone else by writing this blog, and are not liable if anything were to ever occur to anyone. The Author is not financially liable for anything on this site.

**Privacy Policy**  
Surf and Sunshine respects your privacy.  
Any personal information you provide to me including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will _NEVER_ be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of my site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**External Sites/Links**  
Surf and Sunshine is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.  
 ****

**Cookies  
** A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Surf and Sunshine to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.  
 ****

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Surf and Sunshine and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Surf and Sunshine have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.  
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

We share information, we are not responsible for the information that we share and we make no guarantees of the information that we share however we do try our best to make sure information is accurate and up to date. We are not responsible for any damages that are brought to anyone or anything by using this site. User of this site accepts all risks involved with using this website and hold us responsible for nothing.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org
